<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

       <string name="topic_details">
        <![CDATA[

        <h1>Details Screen Help</h1>
        <p>The details screen is design to get a quick run down about your specimen.</p>
        <h2>Entering Information</h2>
        <p>You are able to enter the following details:</p>
        <p><strong>Specimen Type<br />
        </strong><strong>Objective Lens<br />
        </strong><strong>Comments</strong></p>
        <p>Date, Time and GPS data are retrieved from the image"'"s Meta data. </p>
        <p><strong>Date:</strong> Recorded as Day / Month / Year </p>
        <p><strong>Time:</strong> Recorded in 24 hours time HH:MM:SS (eg: 20:50:15 - this would be 8.50pm and 15 seconds)</p>
        <p>If you do not wish for the <strong>GPS</strong> to mark the position please turn it off in you phone settings. </p>
        <p><strong>Please Note:</strong> If you are located in a building the GPS co-ordinates may not register with the phone due to no GPS signal reaching your phone.</p>
        <p><strong>Please Note:</strong> In the case of the objective lens - if  you are not using a microscope to document specimens - you can enter a value of 0</p>
        <br>
        <br>
        <h2>High Resolution Preview &amp; Zoom</h2>
        <p><strong>Step 1.</strong> Click on the image preview<br />
        <strong>Step 2.</strong> The High Resolution page will open<br />
        <strong>Step 3.</strong> Using Pinch Zoom (ie: two fingers) you are able to enlarge and move the image around for a better inspection of the image<br />
        <strong>Step 4.</strong> Press you Back button on your phone to exit this screen</p>
        <p><strong>Note: </strong>On some phones you may have to pinch zoom 3 to 4 times before it will zoom in and out </p>
        <br>
        <br>
        <h2>Using the Side Menu</h2>
        <p>In the side menu (three dots in the top right) you have a number of options:</p>
        <p><strong>Annotate<br />
        Crop<br />
        Save and Upload (User login required)<br />
        Save (Guest login only)<br />
        Restore original<br />
        Delete </strong></p>
        <p><strong>Annotate</strong> - Access the Annotation part of the app. Here you can add arrows, text and scales to your image. To find out more, you can enter the annotation screen and click on the help button.</p>
        <p><strong>Crop</strong> - Crop your image.</p>
        <p><strong>Save and Upload</strong> - Save and upload any details to your online account.</p>
        <p><strong>Save</strong> - Save any details you have entered. This option is for those who are using the app as a GUEST only. Specimen image and details are saved to the phone only.</p>
        <p><strong>Restore original</strong> - Restore your image to the original version.</p>
        <p><strong>Delete</strong> - Delete image and related information. <b>Warning:</b> Once deleted from the phone it cannot be retrieved. However of you have uploaded the image and data to your account, you can access it from the web portal. </p>
        <p><b>Return to the previous screen by touching the Back button.</b>

      ]]>
    </string>



    <string name="topic_annotate">
    <![CDATA[

      <h1>Annotate Screen Help
        </h1>
        <p>Here you are able add annotations your image.</p>
        <h2>Using the Side Menu</h2>
        <p>In the side menu (three&#32;dots&#32;in&#32;the&#32;top&#32;right) you have a number of options:</p>
        <p>  <strong>Save<br />
        Clear</strong></p>
        <p><strong>Save</strong> - Save any annotations you make on the image. Warning: Once saved the only way to clear annotations is to restore your image to its original state.</p>
        <p><strong>Clear</strong> - Clears all annotations made that have not been saved. </p>
        <p><br />
        </p>
        <h2>Adding Arrows, Text and Scale</h2>
        <p><strong>Arrows -</strong> Place arrows to point to parts of your specimen. Press on the icon to view your choice of white or black.</p>
        <p><strong>Text -</strong> Place text to describe parts of your specimen. Press on the icon to view your choice of white or black.</p>
        <p><strong>Scale Bar and Measurement -</strong> Place a scale bar and measurement. Press on the icon to view your choice of white or black. <strong> Please note: </strong> You must calibrate first before you can add a scale bar. If you have not calibrated an error message will appear.</p>
        <p><b>Red Cross, Red Rotate, Red Arrow icons</b></p>
        <p>When adding arrows and text you will see a <strong>red cross icon</strong> , <strong>red rotate icon</strong> and <strong>red arrow icon</strong>. These are there to assist you while using these features.<br />
        <strong><br>Red Cross icon</strong> - deletes the asset you have placed on the image.<br />
        <strong><br>Red Rotate icon</strong> - Press and move to rotate the asset.<br />
        <strong><br>Red Arrow icon</strong> - Press and move in either direction of the red arrows to increase or decrease the size of the asset. </p>
        <p><b>Return to the previous screen by touching the Back button.</b>
      <p>

      ]]>
    </string>











</resources>